{
  "name": "Maths times tables 9 to 12",
  "uniqueid": "a3d2d998-d365-442f-bed6-0e8ea6402da9",
  "enabled": true,
  "questions": [
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 1",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 2",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 3",
      "answer": "27"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 4",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 5",
      "answer": "45"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 6",
      "answer": "54"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 7",
      "answer": "63"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 8",
      "answer": "72"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 9",
      "answer": "81"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 10",
      "answer": "90"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 11",
      "answer": "99"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 x 12",
      "answer": "108"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 1",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 2",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 3",
      "answer": "30"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 4",
      "answer": "40"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 5",
      "answer": "50"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 6",
      "answer": "60"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 7",
      "answer": "70"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 8",
      "answer": "80"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 9",
      "answer": "90"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 10",
      "answer": "100"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 11",
      "answer": "110"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "10 x 12",
      "answer": "120"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 1",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 2",
      "answer": "22"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 3",
      "answer": "33"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 4",
      "answer": "44"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 5",
      "answer": "55"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 6",
      "answer": "66"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 7",
      "answer": "77"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 8",
      "answer": "88"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 9",
      "answer": "99"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 10",
      "answer": "110"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 11",
      "answer": "121"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "11 x 12",
      "answer": "132"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 1",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 2",
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 3",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 4",
      "answer": "48"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 5",
      "answer": "60"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 6",
      "answer": "72"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 7",
      "answer": "84"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 8",
      "answer": "96"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 9",
      "answer": "108"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 10",
      "answer": "120"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 11",
      "answer": "132"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "12 x 12",
      "answer": "144"
    }
  ],
  "rules": {
    "questionsPerGame": 10,
    "answerAlternatives": "11223344556677889900",
    "answerButtonLimit": 5
  },
  "metadata": {
    "targetAges": [
      5,
      6
    ]
  }
}